A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Negatives, 1974-1978
  - EDA Bond signing with British Aircraft Corp., 1976 June 3 (Box 5)
  - Franklin Sherman quilt, 1976 June 14 (Box 5)
  - County Executive Whorton copy neg, Herrity copy neg, 1976 June 21 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Bicentennial Ceremony with Gov. Godwin, 1976 June 29 (Box 5)
  - Judge Hammerswornth(?) as full-time District Court judge, 4-H meat judging winners and scholarship winners with raffled quilt, 1976 July (Box 5)
  - Illustrations for Employee Handbook, 1976 July 9 (Box 5)
  - Sewing for 4-H Fair, Jane Stern, Delligers in Massey Building cafeteria, 1976 July 21 (Box 5)
  - Hazel Shear's Retirement Party, Human Rights Comm-Appointee (Horton, Director), 1976 July 27 (Box 5)
  - John Thillman (O.C.P.), 1976 July 28 (Box 5)
  - Volleyball (County Employees), 1976 July 28 (Box 5)
  - Extension Agent - 4-H Fair, 1976 July 29 (Box 5)
  - Whorton's first day and National Clown Week, 1976 August 2 (Box 5)
  - Linda - Woodrow Wilson Library, 1976 August 31 (Box 5)
  - Bob Atkins Retirement Party, 1976 August 31 (Box 5)
  - Joesph Bertoni, DeZerga, 1976 September 1 (Box 5)
  - Board meeting recognition of: League of Women Voters, Northern Springfield Citizens Association, Carol Whitcombe, 1976 September (Box 5)
  - Group shots of CAA contract signing, 1976 September 13 (Box 5)
  - Proclamation - Fairfax County Symphony, YMCA Parent Child Week, Constitution Week, 1976 September 13 (Box 5)
  - Contract Bidding (Public Works/Capitol Facilities) on Community Center, 1976 September 8 (Box 5)
  - Football Game - Employees (Public Works v. Department of Environment Management), 1976 September 9 (Box 5)
  - Employees at lunch in front of Massey Building, 1976 September 10 (Box 5)
  - Green Pennant Month, Marian Earle Retirement, Proclamation, 1976 September 27 (Box 5)
  - Mount Vernon Hospital Dedication, 1976 October (Box 5)
  - 4-H Week Honorary member of Mr. Herrity, 1976 October (Box 5)
  - Businessman's Aliiance, Hire A Veteran, 1976 October (Box 5)
  - Linda's negs. Courier #10 - Square Dance Caller, Mary Adams, Library, Russians?, Cardiac Arrest Treatment, Dottie and friend, 1976 October 1 (Box 5)
  - Japanese Library, 1976 October 12 - 1976 October 13 (Box 5)
  - Sandy Duckworth Swearing-in, 1976 October 13 (Box 5)
  - Babe Ruth League Honored by Board, 1976 October 18 (Box 5)
  - Employee Football Game - County Executive Office vs. Public Works, 1976 October 18 (Box 5)
  - Onthank Awards, 1976 October 18 (Box 5)
  - Bailey's Community Center Groundbreaking, 1976 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Gatlan(?) at Mental Health Center Tree Planting, 1976 October (Box 5)
  - [Unidentified Board Presentation], 1976 October (?) (Box 5)
  - Animal Shelter; EDC Swearing in Earl Williams, 1976 November 5 (Box 5)
  - James P. McDonald, 1976 November 8 (Box 5)
  - Samuel Finz, 1976 November 8 (Box 5)
  - ACCESS, 1976 November 10 (Box 5)
  - Mr. Stitt County Attorney's Office, 1976 November 12 (Box 5)
  - Herndon Fire Department, Friends of Trees, 1976 November 15 (Box 5)
  - 4-H Meat Awards Christmas Show, 1976 November 16 (Box 5)
  - Sully Plantation, 1976 November 14 (Box 5)
  - Dory Twitched - Bicentennial Ch. portraits/heads, 1976 November 24 (Box 5)
  - Linda - Staff Craft Show, 1976 November 24 (Box 5)
  - Aerial Shots, 1976 November 27 (Box 5)
  - Check presentation to Fairfax County Animal Shelter, Hunter Valley Riding Club, 1976 December 3 (Box 5)
  - Toys for Tots Proclamation, 1976 December 6 (Box 5)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Work Proclamation, Emily Aulsoon(?), Sue Ackley, Jack Herrity, 1976 December 13 (Box 5)
  - Circuit Court Judges, 1976 December 23 (Box 5)
  - Linda - Here is the film from your Friday shooting, 1976 December (Box 5)
  - John Yaremchuk Retirement Party, 1976 December 30 (Box 5)
  - Courthouse Ceiling, 1977 January (Box 5)
  - Reston Center, 1977 January 18 (Box 5)
  - Visitors Center for Don Sweig, 1977 January (Box 5)
  - Tax Assessment explanation for Board, 1977 January 18 (Box 5)
  - Edith Sprouse History Award, 1977 January 18 (Box 5)
  - Marie Turner (Extension Agent) and Personnel Luncheon Meeting at Marco Polo Restaurant, Mrs. Enid Beaumont guest speaker, 1977 January 27 (Box 5)
  - Girl Scouts, 1977 February 4 (Box 5)
  - Black Heritage Week, 1977 February 7 (Box 5)
  - Sleepy Hollow Citizens, 1977 February 7 (Box 5)
  - Employee Service Year Awards, 1977 February (Box 5)
  - Engineers Week, 1977 February 22 (Box 5)
  - Boys - Fire Rescue Proclamation, 1977 February 22 (Box 5)
  - Sealing Time Capsule, 1977 February 22 (Box 5)
  - 4-H Talent, 1977 February (Box 5)
  - Ray Birch Retirement, 1977 March 1 (Box 5)
  - William West 103rd Birthday, 1977 March 3 (Box 5)
  - Judges Swearing-in, 1977 March (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Week, 1977 March (Box 5)
  - Joe Alexander, Beulah Road Project, 1977 March 14 (Box 5)
  - Robinson Rams Proclamation - State Champions/Girls Basketball, 1977 March 28 (Box 5)
  - Austen [Susten?], 1977 April (Box 5)
  - 4-H Fashion Review, 1977 April 2 (Box 5)
  - Mason Neck Ambulance Fund, Cikins/Herrity/Alexander/Flakne, 1977 April 4 (Box 5)
  - West Virginia Salvation Army Proclamation, 1977 April (Box 5)
  - Mary E. Holbein mug (for May 4th Courier), 1977 April (Box 5)
  - County Extension Service Dial-A-Tape, 1977 April? (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - ACCA, Castillo, Clean-Up Day, Mason's?, 1977 April? (Box 5)
  - EAC Pix, 1977 April? (Box 5)
  - Shiva Pant, 1977 April (Box 5)
  - Marion Earle Retirement Party, 1977 April? (Box 5)
  - PLUS Plan Awards, 1977 April? (Box 5)
  - Morrill retirement party, 1977 April 29 (Box 5)
  - Rose Garden [outside Massey Building] [Archie R. Lewis], 1977 May 3 (Box 5)
  - Planning Commission, 1977 May 4 (Box 5)
  - Senior Citizen Fair, 1977 May 6 (Box 5)
  - Transportation Workshop, 1977 May 7 (Box 5)
  - Falls Church High School Band Proclamation, 1977 May 23 (Box 5)
  - Mrs. E. Morrill Retirement Party, 1977 May (Box 5)
  - Dr. Knutson, 1977 May (Box 5)
  - Public Works Week and Exhibit, 1977 June (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - Arthritis Month, Council of the Arts Membership, Cap. Reward/resolution, 1977 June? (Box 5)
  - Courier Pix - Sufferson(?) - Finance, Connor-Public Works, 1977 June? (Box 5)
  - Parks and Recreation Month, 1977 June 6 (Box 5)
  - 4-H Exchange Student and Family, 1977 June 12 (Box 5)
  - Mount Vernon Ped. Clinic, 1977 June 8 (Box 5)
  - Radio Shop opening, 1977 June 16 (Box 5)
  - John Gibb, 1977 June (Box 5)
  - Roger Teller, Mason School Board appointment, 1977 June? (Box 5)
  - Marty Flaherty, 1977 June? (Box 5)
  - EMTA - Vehicles at Newington Garage, 1977 June 2 (Box 5)
  - Housing Proclamation and History Proclamation, 1977 August (Box 5)
  - Retirement - Courier - Ann Davis, 1977 August (Box 5)
  - Voluntary Action Center, 1977 September (Box 5)
  - Mike Gilbert - Manpower Virginia Commission, 1977 September (Box 5)
  - Cutting Curbs/Handicapped, 1977 September (Box 5)
  - Ted Wessell Appointment Comprehensive Planning, 1977 September (Box 5)
  - Neighborhood Improvement Pictures for Sup. Alexander, 1977 September (Box 5)
  - Animal Shelter, 1977 September 29 (Box 5)
  - Fred Kramer - General Services., 1977 September (Box 5)
  - 4-H Award Winner, 1977 September (Box 5)
  - Proclamation / Prof. Women's Week, 1977 October (Box 5)
  - Martha Reeves, 1977 October (Box 5)
  - Assist Inc. Seniors' Transportation, 1977 October? (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - Jobs Month, Energy Month, 1977 October (Box 5)
  - Mary Berger, ORS, 1977 October (Box 5)
  - Howard Cullum, 1977 November (Box 5)
  - Extension Service Emerg/Computer Analysis, 1977 November? (Box 5)
  - Economic Development Authority Tour [Washington Gas and Port Royal Road], 1977 December (Box 5)
  - Extension Service - 4-H Center, 1977 December? (Box 5)
  - Haywood - New Executive Assistant, 1977 December? (Box 5)
  - Onthank Award, 1977 December? (Box 5)
  - Courthouse Ceiling Falls, 1977 December (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - Miss Virginia, Nutrition Week, Engineer Week, Red Cross, United Jewish Appeal, 1978 March (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - West Springfield Drill Team, Spay Neuter Week, 1978 March 27 (Box 5)
  - German Exchange Students visit to Herrity, 1978 March (Box 5)
  - History Display - Sherwood Hall ["Two Notable Fairfax Blacks"], 1978 March (Box 5)
  - CPR Demonstration for Board, Reston Bus Proclamation, 1978 March? (Box 5)
  - Courier - County Nurse Retirees, Tree in Comm., 1978 March? (Box 5)
  - New DEM Director Coons, 1978 March? (Box 5)
  - Human Rights Awards, 1978 March? (Box 5)
  - Proclamation Tootsie Rolls Knights of Columbus, 1978 March (Box 5)
  - Roof shots from Massey Building for Courier, 1978 April (Box 5)
  - League of Women Voters, 1978 April (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - Senior Citizens Month, George Mason University Forensic, Secretaries Week, Walk for Mankind, Good Health Week Feeling fine, 1977 May 2 (Box 5)
  - Mail - Cliff, 1978 October? (Box 5)
  - Proclamation - Supervisors Penino and Travesky with Nancy D. Burleson, Director of District 9 Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1978 October (Box 5)
  - Proclamation - National Friendship Force (Commendation and Endorsement), Linda Chernesky with Chairman Herrity and Sup. Shacochis, 1978 October 16 (Box 5)
  - Bond Sale / Ms. Craigie (award and gift), 1978 October 18 (Box 5)
  - Proclamation - Herrity, 1978 October (Box 5)
  - Symphony Season Opening, 1978 October (Box 5)
  - JOBS Proclamation, 1978 October 30 (Box 5)
  - City-County Luncheon signing services contract, 1978 November (Box 5)
  - Judge Keith (Kieth?), Mr. Hoofnalge and the Lost Minute Book, 1978 November (Box 5)
  - Private Industry Commission organizational meeting, 1979 November (Box 5)
  - Dam Site, 1978 November 30 (Box 5)
  - Ethel Wilcox and Jack Herrity, 1978 (Box 5)
  - New Jail Dedication and interior shots, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Crossroads Proclamation, Jaycess Proclamation, Engineer's Week Proclamation, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Week of Young Child, German Soccer Team, Business/Industry Week, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Annandale School, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Pat Paine, Chappie Cole, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Suggestion Awards [and other unidentified negatives of groups, fire station groundbreaking etc], 1978 (Box 5)
  - [Unidentified Board Proclamations], 1978 (Box 5)
  - [Unidentified Board Proclamations], 1978 (Box 5)
  - [Unidentified Reception in Massey Building], 1978 (Box 5)
- Series 4: Negatives, 1979-1980
  - Animal Shelter, Undated (Box 6)
  - Board of Supervisors - Oath of Office, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Board of Supervisors, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Board of Supervisors - Check presentation from Mason Neck Refuge, Undated (Box 6)
  - Board of Supervisors - Supervisor Moore and Chairman Herrity, Undated (Box 6)
  - Office of Children (Tot Mobile), Undated (Box 6)
  - County Attorney, Undated (Box 6)
  - County Attorney - Henderson, Undated (Box 6)
  - County Executive, Undated (Box 6)
  - Courthouse (old), Undated (Box 6)
  - Courthouse, Undated (Box 6)
  - Juvenile and Domestic Relations, Undated (Box 6)
  - Day Care Center (elderly), 1980 February 4 (Box 6)
  - Employee - Workshop/Seminars, Undated (Box 6)
  - Economic Development Authority Business Week Proclamation 1979, Undated (Box 6)
  - Farmers' Market, 1980 July (Box 6)
  - Health Department - Dental Health Week, 1980 February 7 (Box 6)
  - History - Sections - Liz Davis [probably Liz David], Undated (Box 6)
  - Housing and Community Development - Special program, 1980 June 14 (Box 6)
  - Judge Lewis H. Griffith, Undated (Box 6)
  - New Court House, Undated (Box 6)
  - Court House ground breaking, Undated (Box 6)
  - Judge Lewis H. Griffith taking Oath of Office for the Circuit Court, Undated (Box 6)
  - Judge Joanna F. Fitzpatrick, Undated (Box 6)
  - Judge - Oath Ceremony, Undated (Box 6)
  - Legislators - Package to Richmond, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Ladies who helped at the Board's Oath ceremony, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Land - Smith/Carney Tract, Undated (Box 6)
  - Mount Vernon estate, Undated (Box 6)
  - Mount Vernon Olympic Torch ceremony, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Massey Building, Undated (Box 6)
  - Graduate Minority Internship Program for 1979, 1979 (Box 6)
  - EOC, 1972 July (Box 6)
  - Planning Commission Commissioners taking Oath of Office, Undated (Box 6)
  - Private Industry Commission Organizational Meeting, 1979 November (Box 6)
  - Registrar, Undated (Box 6)
  - Reston Center, Undated (Box 6)
  - I-66 Landfill, Undated (Box 6)
  - Department of Recreation Youth Activities Branch - check presentation for roving leader program, Undated (Box 6)
  - Social Services, Undated (Box 6)
  - Soil and Water District, Undated (Box 6)
  - Special Projects - visiting official observing Fairfax County operations, 1979 April 25 (Box 6)
  - Social Services - Award Ceremony for Volunteers, Undated (Box 6)
  - Tornado - 1979 David, Undated (Box 6)
  - Women's Re-entry Center, Undated (Box 6)
- Series 5: Negatives, 1980-1986
  - Proclamation, 1980 February 4 (Box 7)
  - George Washington's Birthday, 1980 February (Box 7)
  - County Attorney's Office - Zoning Case, 1980 February (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Black History, CETA Awards, Honor Boys, 1980 February (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 March (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 April (Box 7)
  - Purchasing County Stickers, 1980 April (Box 7)
  - Older Americans Month, 1980 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 May 18 (Box 7)
  - J. Hamilton Lambert, 1980 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 June (Box 7)
  - R. Page Ret School Board, 1980 June (Box 7)
  - Metro Construction Inspection, 1980 June (Box 7)
  - Proclamation: James Madison Band, 1980 June (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 July (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 July (Box 7)
  - Red Cross - Certificate of Merit Award (Fairfax County Chapter), 1980 July 14 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1980 August (Box 7)
  - Crime Solvers promo tape for TV, 1980 August (Box 7)
  - Board Meeting, 1980 August (Box 7)
  - Judicial Center construction, 1980 August (Box 7)
  - Proclamation: Dranesville District Softball Champs; Visiting Nurses; Earl Williams resigns EDA; Northern Virginia Community Foundation Week, 1980 September (Box 7)
  - Warren Hutchinson certificate of conformance from MFOA, 1980 September (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Fire Prevention Month etc., 1980 October (Box 7)
  - Conservation Week, 1980 October (Box 7)
  - Check Presentation Mason's Neck Park, 1980 October (Box 7)
  - J. Hamilton Lambert's Birthday party, 1980 November (Box 7)
  - Assessments - Visiting Officials, 1980 November 24 (Box 7)
  - CAA New Members, 1980 December (Box 7)
  - Metro Tour by Board of Supervisors, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations Misc., 1980 (Box 7)
  - Tree Commission, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Personnel - Department Heads and Sam Finz, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Onthank Awards, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Plant Nursery, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Budget Meeting, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Center Opening, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Assessments, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Purchasing Director, 1980 (Box 7)
  - OMB, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Proclamation, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Reston dump, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Planning Commission, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Jane Stern Public Affairs, 1981 January (Box 7)
  - Fairfax-Falls Church Community Services Board & Supervisors sign agreement, 1981 January (Box 7)
  - Sup. Davis oath of office (magistrate), 1981 January (Box 7)
  - Proclamation: Mental Health Month, 1981 January (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 January-February (Box 7)
  - Energy Awards, 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Ted Wessel with visiting officials, 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Planning Commission, 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Providence District Trails Ceremony (Sup. Scott), 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Board Workshop (Dulles Marriott Hotel) with George Mason University, 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Board meets with George Mason Public Affairs office, 1981 February (Box 7)
  - George Washington Birthday, 1981 February 22 (Box 7)
  - Litter Control Proclamation, 1981 March (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Red Cross Month, Medical Record Week, 1981 March 9 (Box 7)
  - Supervisor James P. Scott, 1981 March (Box 7)
  - Office for Children, 1981 March 27 (Box 7)
  - Social Services Award, 1981 March (Box 7)
  - Juvenile Detention Center groundbreaking ceremony, 1981 March (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 April (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 April (Box 7)
  - Sup. Travesky talks to 4th graders, 1981 April (Box 7)
  - Cable TV Seminar, 1981 April (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 April (Box 7)
  - Arbor Day, 1981 April 22 (Box 7)
  - Col. Richard King appointed Deputy County Executive, 1981 May (Box 7)
  - Miss Teen Proclamation, 1981 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamation, 1981 May (Box 7)
  - Bill Rucker (Courier story - Bill passed the bar exam), 1981 May (Box 7)
  - Verdia Haywood appointed Deputy County Executive, 1981 May (Box 7)
  - Commission for Women Awards, 1981 June (Box 7)
  - Sewage Agreement for Northern Virginia, 1981 June (Box 7)
  - Planning Commission taking oath, 1981 June (Box 7)
  - Real Estate Assessments Sam Patterson, 1981 June (Box 7)
  - Proclamation (History Week), 1981 July (Box 7)
  - Proclamation, 1981 July (Box 7)
  - Purchasing Director receives award, 1981 July (Box 7)
  - George Washington will Clerk Hoofnagle, 1981 August (Box 7)
  - Warren Hutchison receives award [Director of Finance], 1981 August (Box 7)
  - Fire Prevention Week, Baseball team honored, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Tim Jones named Director of ORS, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Dave Sheatsley ORS, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Condo Conversion Agreement signed, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - EAC, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Planning Commission taking oath, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Proclamation for Wolf Trap anniversary, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Volunteer Action Center, Drafting Week, 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Historical Map, 1981 October (Box 7)
  - Juvenile Detention Center, 1981 October (Box 7)
  - Water Conservation Dir. Proclamation, 1981 October (Box 7)
  - Hinkle Press Room, 1981 October (Box 7)
  - Agreement for condo conversion, 1981 October (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 October (Box 7)
  - Sup. Duckworth presenting TV, 1981 November (Box 7)
  - J. Lambert's Birthday Party, 1981 November (Box 7)
  - Older Worker Week, 1981 November (Box 7)
  - Sup. Travesky with Springfield cub scouts, 1981 November 17 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Easter Seal, Civil Air Defense, 1981 November 23 (Box 7)
  - Special Project for Pat McDonald ["This space reserved for Walter Craigie ' A Virginia Gentleman'" sign], 1981 December (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1981 December (Box 7)
  - E-911 Starts, 1981 December (Box 7)
  - Chairman Herrity, 1981 December (Box 7)
  - Commission for Women, 1981 (Box 7)
  - EMTA Garage, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Mount Vernon Center Groundbreaking, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Proclamation, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Lenny Skutnik Ceremony, 1982 January (Box 7)
  - Handicapped Month, 1982 January (Box 7)
  - Springfield Commuter Parking, 1982 January (Box 7)
  - Archaeology Display, 1982 January (Box 7)
  - Proclamation United Jewish Appeal, 1982 January 5 (Box 7)
  - Land Dedication - Special Ceremony in Marie Travesky's office for church group, 1982 January (Box 7)
  - Proclamations - History Commission for George Washington, Martin Luthrum Birthday, Dental Week, 1982 January (Box 7)
  - Crime Prevention Week Proclamation, 1982 February 8 (Box 7)
  - Zoning Inspector enforcing sign ordinance, 1982 February (Box 7)
  - Special Signing Ceremony with Sup. Travesky, 1982 February (Box 7)
  - Sup. Travesky's Staff, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Sup. Davis new baby, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Handicapped Outreach Program, 1982 March 1 (Box 7)
  - Women's History Week, 1982 March 1 (Box 7)
  - Red Cross Month, 1982 March 1 (Box 7)
  - Lee District pot holes, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Proclamation Older Worker Week, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Historical Building old Sheriff's house [Old Fairfax County Jail], 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Director of Public Affairs, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Tim Shimer's(?) Going Away Party, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - KOVAR Tootsie Roll Week Knights of Columbus Centennial, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Sam Huff, National Year of the Eagle, Mount Vernon students present report, 1982 March (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Amateur Radio Day, Health Fair '82, Special Olympics Day?, 1982 March 22 (Box 7)
  - March of Dimes child, Proclamation: Fair Housing Month, 1982 April 5 (Box 7)
  - 3 cars with tree damage, 1982 April 6 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Co-Op, Chamber of Commerce, 1982 April 12 (Box 7)
  - Swearing-in Judge Davis, People lines for county tags, 1982 April 12 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Keep Fairfax County Beautiful (Litter Task Force), Volunteer Service, 1982 April 19 (Box 7)
  - Edith Register and Herrity - Municipal clerk certificate, Sanda Duckworth and Dr. D. swearing-in by Hoofnagle - Governor's Block Grant Committee, 1982 April 22 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations, 1982 April 26 (Box 7)
  - Board of Supervisors Arbor Day - Massey Building, 1982 April 26 (Box 7)
  - Nancy Falck's Arbor Day Tree Planting, 1982 April 28 (Box 7)
  - New Courthouse, 1982 April 29 (Box 7)
  - Denton Kent new appointer, 1982 April 30 (Box 7)
  - Arbor Day Plantings - Travesky, Duckworth, 1982 April 30 (Box 7)
  - Gypsy Moths - Egg Masses, 1982 May (Box 7)
  - Disgruntled Motorist, 1982 May (Box 7)
  - Carpool/Vanpool, 1982 May (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: National Year of Disabled, Adult Continuing Education, Mental Health Month, 1982 May 3 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Small Business Week, Medical Record Practioners Week, Municipal Clerk's Week, 1982 May 10 (Box 7)
  - Gypsy Moth Spraying - Great Falls/Springfield, 1982 May 11 (Box 7)
  - Students visit Ethel and the Clerk's Office, 1982 May 12 (Box 7)
  - Supervisor Alexander's negatives, 1982 May (Box 7)
  - Herrity receiving check donation, 1982 May 11 (Box 7)
  - U.S.S. Fairfax County, 1982 May 13 (Box 7)
  - Outstanding Fairfax Women (Session 1 & 2), 1982 May 14-15 (Box 7)
  - Outstanding Fairfax Women (Session 3) - Sharon Figer, Kim Ritchie, Cornelia Suhler, Marjorie Morrison, Emilie Miller, Flore Crater, Barb Hildreth, 1982 May 19 (Box 7)
  - Outstanding Fairfax Women (Session 4) - Dr. Magno, Nancy James, Cathy Cockrill, Nancy White, 1982 May 20 (Box 7)
  - Mrs. Shouse, 1982 May (Box 7)
  - Hoofnagle, Circuit Court Judges, 1982 May (Box 7)
  - Softball Proclamations, Gary Schaffenberger, William Austin, 1982 May 24 (Box 7)
  - Travesky / kids, 1982 June 1 (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Trici Higginbottom, Sesame Street Children's Fire Safety Week, Safe Boating, Child Abuse, Dr. Claude Mason(?), 1982 June 7 (Box 7)
  - Retake Fairfax Women, 1982 June (Box 7)
  - Seal in Board Room, 1982 June (Box 7)
  - Proclamations: Mobil Oil, Principal of South Lakes, Apnea, 1982 June 21 (Box 7)
  - Outdoor Testing for New Camera, 1982 June (Box 7)
  - Judge Hammer Swearing-in, 1982 June 28 (Box 7)
  - Massey Portrait Unveiling, 1982 June 28 (Box 7)
  - 2 Proclamations: Eltsi(?) Carter, Independence Week, 1982 June 28 (Box 7)
  - Courthouse - Sam, 1982 July (Box 7)
  - Millie Valla Retirement, 1982 July (Box 7)
  - Navy Elementary Certificate Presentation - Herrity, 1982 July 8 (Box 7)
  - Retirement of Herrity staff person, 1982 July 9 (Box 7)
  - Gypsy Moth parasites released, 1982 July 9 (Box 7)
  - George Washington bust and will (taken for Donald Sweig and Liz David), 1982 July 13 (Box 7)
  - CPR, 1982 July 19 (Box 7)
  - Ribbon-cutting Clayborne Avenue - Sam, Alexander, 1982 July 23 (Box 7)
  - Sheriff Huggins - NACO Award, 3 proclamations - Liz Dorson, Laura McDowell, George Lovelace, 1982 July 26 (Box 7)
  - Foreign Exchange Boy Scouts (Travesky), 1982 July 29 (Box 7)
  - Fairfax Babe Ruth Baseball Team, 1982 July 30 (Box 7)